Hi. So I recently got back into playing
Magic the Gathering. I haven't played since high
school, and I met some new friends here
that play, and it's really fun. So I've
been playing commander, and I did get the
start of a, Sephiroth commander, deck. And, you
know, one of the fun things about magic
is, like, all of the beautiful card sleeves
and and dice and placemats and all the,
like, beautiful things that you can buy to
have, like, a really cool setup. Obviously, I'm
very interested in that, but I kind of
wanted to get into it and set some
you know, just have my little setup without
having to, like, spend a bunch on a
new hobby. So I did that today. I
had this old box from Container Store, and
I covered it with this, washi paper that
I also had, this Japanese, paper, just with
glue. It's really easy to do, and so
that's kinda my my box. And then what
I put in it is, my commander deck.
I'm my Sephiroth deck I'm keeping in this.
This was, originally a Japanese stationery set, and
and I kept the box because it was
so pretty. And it's really good for holding
my card. So I'll I will show you
Sephiroth. Here he is in all his glory.
Oh, is he? And oh, and I'll just
show you one other card that I absolutely
love. Where is she? I really wanna build
a Hatsune Miku deck, just for the vibes,
and there's this one counterspell card that I
got. Where are you? So many rats. So
many rats and goblins. Not goblins. Where are
you, Hatsune? Oh my gosh. Here she is.
Look at this counterspell. She's so cute. She's
like that's like a a horned paparazzi. Adorable.
Anyhoo. Sorry. Getting sidetracked. So, yeah, in my
deck, I have my commander deck. I'm storing
it here, for now. And then I have
this was also a stationary box. I really
like saving boxes for things like this because
you never know when they're gonna come in
handy. It's the perfect fit for all of
my other cards, that are just, like, not
I'm not haven't really built into a deck
yet. And then someone got me a gift
that had, like, a little jewelry bag with
it, so I kept that. And, I'm using
it to store these d and d dice
that I got at the Washington Wren Fair,
that are fairy fire themed. I rolled a
d 20 when I picked I picked them
up, so I was like and I didn't
have, like, a fancy set yet, so I
was like, I gotta have them. And then,
I'm keeping my token cards in here. I
feel like token cards would be really fun
to make some custom ones, but we'll we'll
get to that. And then this is not
really useful in any way, but, I got
this Sailor Moon figurine. She's, like, made out
of, like I think she's made out of
crystal. I'm not sure. She could be just,
like, very convincing cold plastic. I got her
when I lived in LA, and I just
was like, she's cute. I could just, like,
put her out in my air like, my
area to feel good about my life when
I'm playing, Magic. So, yeah, that is my
setup. It took me, like, an you know,
less than an hour to kind of get
all this together from stuff that I had,
and I'm really happy with it for now.
So, yay. And I'm actually in the car
on the way to go and play some
magic. So yeah. Bye.